Your media player does not support the subtitle format used in this episode. Subtitles will likely not function properly. Please use one of the recommended video players, preferably mpv: https://mpv.io
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Just in time.
Zamanında yetiştim.
Luffy...
Luffy-san...
Pell...
Pell...
There's not much time until the square is blown up...
Meydanın havaya uçmasına çok az zaman kaldı...
Everyone...
Herkes...
has already fallen...
ölecek!
No one can hear me anymore...
Sesim kimseye ulaşmıyor.
At this rate, the country will...
Bu durumda, ülke...
Don't worry.
Endişelenme.
We can hear your voice!
Biz seni gayet iyi duyabiliyoruz!
Again, I'm obviously way more injured than you!
Yine söylüyorum, yaralarım seninkilerden daha berbat durumda!
Oh, I feel faint. This is bad...
Ah, bayılacağım.
Yeah, right!
Yalancı!
Be careful, Luffy.
Dikkatli ol, Luffy-kun.
I ate lots of meat, so I got lots of blood!
Bir ton et yedim. Çok fazla enerjim var!
I won't...
Bir daha...
lose again!
kaybetmeyeceğim!
How did he get out of that quicksand with those injuries...?
O yaralarla batan kumdan nasıl kaçabildi?
Luffy's alive!
Luffy yaşıyor!
Tony!
Tony-kun!
Wh-Wh-What?!
N-N-N-Ne?!
Luffy!
Luffy!
Vivi's here, too!
Vivi de orada!
See?! See?! I told you! I knew it!
Gö-Gördün mü?! Yaşadığını söylemiştim! Ondan hiç şüphe etmedim!
Really?
Öyle mi?
You sure don't look like someone who knew.
Yüzündeki ifadeye bakılırsa öyle düşünmüyordun.
Usopp! Sanji!
Usopp-san, Sanji-san!
What happened, my sweet Vivi?!
Oh! Ne oldu, Vivi-chan?!
You're hurt so bad!
Çok kötü yaralanmışsın!
Usopp!
Usopp!
Nami... Mr. Bushido...
Nami-san, Bay Bushido...
Everyone's okay...
Herkes güvende!
Who asked you to make some party prop?!
Parti numaraları için oyuncak yapmanı kim söyledi?!
How the hell are you standing?!
Ayakta durabildiğini biliyordum!
Nami my love!
Nami-swaan!
I-It had that crazy strong attack though, right?
A-Ama işini gördü, değil mi?
I'll deal with you later!
Seninle sonra görüşeceğim!
Vivi...
Vivi...
What's with this sandstorm? Do you know what's going on?
Neler oluyor? Bu kum fırtınası da ne?!
Yes...
Evet...
Hey, jackass!
Hey, budala!
Why is my precious Nami injured?!
Nami-san, nasıl yaralandı?!
I'm gonna gut you!
Seni öldüreceğim!
She's just fine, isn't she...?
Hiçbir şeyi yok!
Chopper, do me one last favor...
Chopper, bana bir iyilik yap.
Will you please bury my body out in the desert...?
Lütfen bedenimi çöle gömer misin?
His wounds were fatal!
Aniden ölümcül yaralarına yenik düştü!
Sorry, guys.
Üzgünüm, çocuklar.
He beat me last time.
Ona karşı durdum ve yenildim.
But...
Bu yüzden bir daha...
I won't lose again!
yenilmeyeceğim!
I'll leave the rest to you!
Gerisi sizde!
Just go already.
Bir an önce git.
If you can't win...
Sen onu yenemezsen...
who the hell can?!
kim yenebilir?!
I'm gonna put an end...
Şuna kesin olarak...
to all this!
bir son verelim!
– Yeah!
– Evet!
Everyone...
Hepiniz...
I'm glad I still have...
Burada hâlâ arkadaşlarım var.
You bastard!
Seni piç!
Flail all you want, but you won't be able to hit me.
Kaç kez dövüşürsek dövüşelim, bana bir kez bile vuramayacaksın!
Looks like you want to be skewered again.
Yine şişlenmek istiyorsun galiba.
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Who in the world is that?!
O da kim?!
Could he have...?!
Yoksa o...?!
Buzzsaw!
Daire Testere!
He hit Crocodile...!
Crocodile'a vurdu!
Well, well...
Vay vay...
Get up.
Ayağa kalk.
It all clicked when that water from Yuba got on your hand...
Yuba suyunun eline dökülmesiyle her şey çözüldü.
When you get wet, you can't turn into sand!
Su sana değerse kuma dönüşemezsin.
You stole the rain cause you're afraid of water, didn't you?
Sudan korkuyorsun, değil mi? Bu yüzden yağmuru çaldın.
Now I can kick your ass.
Şimdi seni mahvedebilirim.
The real fight starts now.
Gerçek dövüşe hazır ol.
What?!
Ne dedin sen?!
They're gonna bomb the square in ten minutes?!
Meydan on dakika içinde bombalanacak mı?
Ten minutes?!
10 dakikada mı?!
No time to think, huh?!
Bunu düşünecek vaktimiz yok!
But if the diameter is five kilometers,
Ama 5 kilometre çapında bir patlamaysa...
the guy firing would have to be two and a half kilometers from here, right?!
en azından 2,5 kilometre uzaktan atıyor olmalılar, değil mi?
No, I doubt that!
Hayır, öyle değil.
The cannoneer is most likely near the square!
Bombacılar daha çok meydana yakın olacak gibi!
What?! Why?!
Ne?! Neden?!
If so, then they'd get caught in the explosion!
Öyleyse, bombacılar da herkesle birlikte havaya uçacak!
That's the kind of man Crocodile is...
Crocodile böyle bir adam.
He doesn't care if his own soldiers die?!
Kendi adamlarını mı öldürtecek?!
What a crafty bastard...
Kurnaz piç...
Let's go already!
Acele etsek iyi olur.
We found you, Princess Vivi!
Seni bulduk, Prenses Vivi!
I wonder how big of a promotion I'll get if I kill you...
Ölümün bize büyük bir terfi sağlayacak!
Billions!
Milyarlar!
Ten minutes minus... how many seconds?
On dakika kaç saniyedir?
Hey, we're wasting time talking.
Hey, hey! Bunu bile konuşacak zamanımız yok!
Two seconds max!
2 saniye!
I'll go on ahead!
Önden gideceğim!
– I'll go too!
– Ben de!
Don't slow down, idiot!
Yavaşlama, sersem!
Let's split up! We can't do anything until we're out of this storm!
Herkes ayrılsın! Bu lanet kum fırtınasından çıkmalıyız!
Ten more minutes...!
Sadece on dakika!
Okay, hurry up! Let's go!
Tamam, acele et! Gitmeliyiz!
Yeah!
Evet!
This truly is... our last chance!
Bu son şansımız!
The next ten minutes...
Ülkenin kaderi...
will decide this country's fate...!
on dakika içinde belli olacak!
You really think you can beat me?
Beni yenebileceğini mi düşünüyorsun?
Yeah.
Evet.
I am impressed you figured it out, especially so close to death...
Ölümün eşiğindeyken bunu anlamış olmandan epey etkilendim.
But that's still nowhere near enough to put you on my level—
Ama bu seni hâlâ benim seviyeme çıkarmaz—
the level of the Seven Warlords.
Bir Shichibukai seviyesine.
So what if you're one of the Seven Warlords?
Shichibukai'ysen ne olmuş?
Then, that makes me...
Öyleyse ben...
the eighth Warlord!
Hachibukai'yim!
Who in the world is that man?
Kim bu adam Tanrı aşkına?!
He's a pirate.
Korsan.
Haven't you heard?
Hiç duymadın mı?
Looks like the princess escaped death once again.
Prenses bir kez daha ucu ucuna ölümden kaçmış gibi görünüyor.
Then he must be the one who brought Vivi back...
Öyleyse Vivi'yi buraya getiren kişi o olmalı.
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Pistol!
Tabanca!
Your strategy fails if I just dodge your attacks.
Saldırılarını atlatırsam stratejin bir işe yaramaz.
Whether it's wet or not...
Suyla kaplanmış bile olsan,
my hand can absorb any kind of fluid.
yine de ellerimle seni kurutabilirim!
Sh-Shoot! I forgot he could do that!
K-Kahretsin! Hâlâ bunu yapabiliyor!
You said it yourself, didn't you?
Bunu söyleyen sendin, değil mi?
Devil fruit abilities can be...
Şeytan Meyvesi'nin yeteneği...
as strong as any weapon.
nasıl kullandığına bağlı olarak,
It just depends on how you use it.
daha da gelişebilir.
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Lastik-Lastik Tabanca!
Shotgun!
Çifte Tabanca!
Impudent brat!
Arsız velet!
Desert Spada!
Çöl Kılıcı!
That thing again?!
Yine mi o?!
That was close...
Çok yakındı...
Gum-Gum...!
Lastik-Lastik...!
The same technique over and over again...
Aynı saldırıları tekrar tekrar kullanarak,
Are you even trying to win?
kazanabilir misin?
Yeah!
Evet!
I sure am!
Kazanacağım!
This was my goal from the start!
Başından beri bunu planlıyordum!
Time to get soaked!
Seni suyla kaplayacağım!
I saw that coming from a mile away!
Ne anlaşılır bir strateji!
Sables!
Kum Fırtınası!
Come back, barrel!
Fıçı! Fıçı!
You're struggling desperately, Straw Hat Luffy...
Ne kadar umutsuzsun, Hasır Şapka luffy!
See, you've become too reliant on that barrel.
Fıçı olmadan hiçbir şey yapamazsın.
This isn't any different from our first fight.
Bu dövüşün ilk kapışmamızdan hiçbir farkı yok.
You're right.
Haklısın.
Nothing's changed yet.
Şimdiye dek hiçbir şey değişmedi.
Well, how about this?!
Ya şimdi?!
I'm way different now.
Artık önceki gibi değilim!
Are you serious?
Delirdin mi sen?
Water Luffy!
Su Luffy!
Oh no! This is bad! I sprung a leak!
Ah! Kahretsin! Sızdırıyorum!
Is this brat...
Bu velet...
messing with me...?
ciddi mi?
Belly's sloshing around...
Karnım suyla doldu...
I guess I drank too much...
Çok içtim galiba...
Does he not understand the gravity of the situation?
İçinde bulunduğu durumu anlamıyor mu?
Stop playing around, you damn brat!
Bu kadar oyun yeter, velet!
Dammit!
Kahretsin!
Who's playing around?!
Oynayan kimmiş?
My body...
Bedenim...
I'm always serious!
Ben her zaman ciddiyim!
Gum-Gum...
Lastik-Lastik...
Bazooka!
Bazuka!
How's that... sandodile?!
Nasıldı, Kumcroc?
I can't believe it...!
İnanılmaz...!
Crocodile was actually beaten...?
Crocodile'ı dövüyor...
This is no time to be impressed, right, Mr. Cobra?
Etkilenecek zaman değil, Bay Cobra.
Now, you're going to take me...
Şimdi beni, poneglifin olduğu...
to the poneglyph!
yere götüreceksin.
Why do you want to see something like that?
Onu görmek sana ne kazandıracak?
Don't ask pointless questions.
Aptalca sorular sorma.
All you have to do is lead the way.
Sadece yolu göster.
I wonder if your luck is running out...
Hiç şansın kalmadı...
There isn't much time left.
Çok zamanın yok.
Go already, Nico Robin...
Git buradan, Nico Robin.
unless you wish to wither away as well.
Tabii sen de kurumak istemiyorsan.
My patience... is running thin...
Artık... sabrımı yitirdim.
Nico Robin?!
Nico Robin mi?!
Very well. As you wish.
Pekâlâ. Nasıl isterseniz.
Listen carefully, Straw Hat.
Dinle, Hasır Şapka.
Even the rock in this courtyard...
Buradaki tüm kayaları...
can wither away.
un ufak edeceğim.
The grass is drying up!
Otlar kuruyor!
Ground Secco!
Kurutma!
What the heck...?!
Ne oluyor...?!
I'm falling!
Düşüyorum!
Th-That was close!
U-Ucuz kurtuldum!
That big jerk!
Lanet olası!
Water-Water Pistol!
Su-Su Tabanca!
What?! He swallowed it with his hand!
Ne?! Suyu eliyle emdi!
You thought you nullified my powers, "Water Luffy"...?
Yeteneğimi engellemeye mi çalışıyorsun, Su Luffy?
That was a grave mistake.
Öyleyse, üzücü bir biçimde hatalısın.
The true power of sand is dehydration.
Kumun gücü, mutlak kuruluğunda yatmaktadır.
Behold.
İzle!
My right hand dries out everything...
Bu sağ el dokunduğu her şeye kuruluk bahşediyor.
There's no limit to its power.
Sınırsız olarak.
The rock...
Kayalar...
Even statues are turning into sand...
Heykeller bile kuma dönüşüyor!
The ground...
Yer...
is dying...!
kuruyor!
Even my sandles!
Terliklerim bile!
Everything connected to this hand...
Bu elin dokunduğu her şey...
will shrivel up and die!
kurur!
Ground Death!
Erozyon Döngüsü!
You picked a perfect time to show up, Marines.
Tam zamanında geldiniz, Denizciler.
Out of the way. We're in a hurry.
Çekilin. Acelem var.
I'm afraid we can't!
Bunu yapamam!
I heard the situation from a soldier here in Alubarna.
Yaralı bir asker, Alubarna'da olan biten her şeyi anlattı!
Who do you think that person is?!
O adamın kim olduğunu sanıyorsun?!
Well, I don't care who he is.
Kim olduğu önemli değil.
I hate people in the government.
Hükûmetle ilişkisi olanlardan nefret ediyorum.
If you don't get out of my way...
Geçmeme izin vermezseniz...
We have no intention of letting you pass!
Geçmene izin vermek niyetinde değilim!
Then I'll simply kill you.
Öyleyse, hepinizi öldürmek zorundayım.
Wait, Marines! Don't worry about me!
Denizciler, durun! Bana ne olduğu önemli değil!
We were told a cannon will be fired at 4:30
İsyanın patlak verdiği saray meydanı...
right into the palace square where the rebellion is happening!
tam 4:30'da bir patlama tarafından yutulacak!
Please, you must find a way to stop it!
Lütfen, patlamayı durdurmalısınız!
What...?!
Ne...?!
Only seven minutes...!
7 dakika sonra...!
A million citizens' lives are at stake!
Bir milyon insanımın hayatı tehlikede!
Even so...
Ama...
We'll save you, then stop the explosion!
Önce seni kurtaralım, sonra patlamayı durdururuz!
Wait! This woman is–
Durun! Bu kadın–
Ready!
Hazırlanın!
Don't get in my way!
Yoluma çıkmayın!
Treinta Fleurs!
30 Çiçek!
Strangle!
Boğma!
A devil fruit...!
Şeytan meyvesi...!
I said I was in a hurry, didn't I?!
Acelem var demiştim, değil mi?
Don't make me upset!
Beni daha fazla kızdırmayın!
Sergeant Major!
Başçavuş!
This woman is Nico Robin!
Bu kadın, Nico Robin!
I'm sure of it!
Eminim!
Per Captain Smoker's orders, I looked for her wanted poster.
Albay Smoker, onun aranıyor posterlerini asmamı söylemişti!
She has a bounty on her head!
Bu kadının kellesine...
She was known all over the world twenty years ago!
yirmi yıl önce dünya çapında büyük bir ödül konuldu!
I remember reading about it in the papers at the time.
Gazete yazısını bile hatırlıyorum.
There was an incident where six Marine warships were sunk.
Altı Donanma savaş gemisinin batırıldığı olayın faili oydu.
They said it was the work of a single eight-year-old girl!
Bunu yaparken henüz sadece sekiz yaşındaydı.
The government declared her a significant risk,
Hükûmet tarafından üst düzey bir suçlu olarak ilan edildi...
and the bounty given was a whopping 79 million belly!
ve kellesine 79 milyon beli ödül kondu!
However, she suddenly disappeared after that.
Bunun ardından, hiçbir iz bırakmadan ortadan kayboldu.
Stop your rambling!
Gevezeliği kes!
Will you clear the way, or will you die?! Which is it?!
Çekilin ya da ölün! Hangisi?
Numbers don't matter against her...
Sayımızı dert etmiyor gibi görünüyor.
Sergeant! Take everyone to the square and stop the explosion!
Çavuş! Herkesi meydana götür ve patlamayı durdur!
But, Sergeant Major...!
Ama, Başçavuş...!
Hurry! There're only six minutes left!
Çabuk! Sadece altı dakika kaldı!
Yes, ma'am!
Başüstüne!
Now, let that man go!
Şimdi, bırak onu!
I told you not to get in my way!
Seni uyardım!
That was close!
Ucuz atlattım.
His right hand is a real problem...
Sağ eli çok tehlikeli...
The lawn turned into a desert!
Bahçe çöle döndü.
Where'd he go?
Nereye gitti bu?
You made me waste my energy...
Kendimi çok fazla zorlamama neden oldun.
You missed...
Iskaladın.
Croco...
Croco...
Once again...
Bir kez daha...
you lose...
kaybettin,
Straw Hat Luffy.
Hasır Şapkalı Luffy.